Kyouka, I want to borrow Yuki.
I think we should know what my
slave form is like, shouldn't we?
You couldn't handle rewarding him.
Don't worry about it.
Bring it on!
I've made up my mind!
I want more weapons in my arsenal!
Good point.
Judging by her behavior in default form,
Kusetsu was most likely a newborn
amongst the eight thunder gods.
It's safe to assume that the remaining
gods are stronger than she was.
Lives are at stake here.
Yuki, we need to be as strong as possible.
Right.
The reason my life is this way?
I know is all because of you.
Those were your words!
So I'm okay with this.
I want Mato to borrow you?
Mato?
Got it!
He can change into something like that.
It makes sense. Right. Up my alley!
All right. Yuki.
Let's go for a ride.
You good down there? Yeah!
This speed is great!
The breeze in Mato isn't so bad, huh?
I've always thought
motorcycles were really cool.
I wanted to learn how to ride one so
I could take a girl out on a date.
Now that you've warmed up, let's see, what
kind of tricks you've got up your sleeve?
A crew of Chugi!
Seems like they're not fans
of the noise, are they?
Take these guys out!
Let's rest things up a bit!
Run him over, Yuki!
A one-hit kill!
You holding up okay?
I can keep going!
Nice!
Then let's patrol the second squadron!
Yes, ma 'am!
You held out all the way to the dorm!
We can flush our enemies out
of hiding with all the noise!
It's strong and durable, too!
Oh, not too shabby.
Let's take a break in the car.
I guess it's time for
your reward to begin.
So this is it?
What kind of a reward is this?
It feels like a date.
Oh yeah,
this isn't so bad after all.
Here, uh, thank you that's so nice.
Wait, why did I hand him my drink?
This is almost like an indirect kiss.
How is this happening?
Let, let me have yours.
This is really kicking my ass!
That was a piece of cake.
I guess there's still more to it, huh?
Are you feeling okay?
I'm fine, goddammit!
Are we really doing this?
I can't believe I'm
letting a man see me naked!
I'll give you a real kiss, Yuki.
If I go this far,
I have to accept the consequences.
Well, I'm glad Mato is feeling better.
I…
I wonder how my sister
and the others are doing.
Huh?
Miss Tenka?
Shhh!
Uh...
Hmm...
Huh?
There he is!
Big sis! Coco! Nan!
I love that I can feel my little
brother's strength returning.
I'm so glad you're safe and sound.
Getting to Yokohama and back
was easy thanks to Tenka.
What?
What do you mean there and back?
You brought her there?
I had a feeling when I discovered that
our enemy could face through matter.
I figured Alba and her friends
were probably linked somehow.
And boy, she hit the nail on the head.
Tenka's been bringing us all
sorts of goodies for a while now.
I had no idea.
Flying solo is usually the best way to
minimize the risk involved. That's why.
I did it this way because I knew that
you'd be worried for their well-being.
Nice one, Tenka!
Thank you so much, Ms. Tenka!
It's important to always
look out for one another.
We owe you a big thank
you as well, so thank you!
Thank you, Yuki.
Oh, it wasn't me.
If anything, it was all Ms.
Kyoka.
Don't be so modest!
We heard about it from Aholba.
She told us that it was
truly quite the rescue.
Magnificent?
Seriously, Ms.
Kyouka was the real hero!
Tenka, got a sec?
Is the Demon Defense Force
going to show up on my doorstep?
Well, at the moment,
the Defense Force is dealing
with the threat of the Eight
Thunder Gods and their new
method of deploying Shuki.
We're pretty swamped right now.
You'll be okay.
I guess even your organization
has some adjustments to make.
We still haven't found
any leads on turning
you and your friends back
into humans quite yet.
I'll keep trying to probe for
information on the Onmio Bureau, but...
Seems like it's going to take some time.
Might be best if we move to a
different hideout, just in case.
Right now, just having Coco and now on
back safe and sound is a five-star rating.
Are you two feeling alright
now that you're back?
Luckily, we're not injured.
Just a bit lethargic.
We've already improved a
lot since getting back here.
Maybe there's something
I can do to help you.
You give wonderful massages.
Their pressure points, the
ins and outs of their bodies.
Somehow, I know every part of them.
Is it because Kusetsu is inside
of me, and she was one with them?
Wow!
I feel like a brand new person!
Happy to hear it!
All's well that ends well,
but I faced plenty of challenges
during the Yokohama fight.
I'd better lock in!
I'll see you at the next
commander's meeting.
Good night.
Okay.
Thanks for everything, Miss Tenka.
Bye.
Alba.
A bunch of Shuki raining
down on a big city?
The whole world is in a giant uproar.
Making all those appearances, to put
everyone's mind at ease, must be very hectic.
You did a great job. Yes, indeed.
Perhaps you can help me
blow off some steam later.
Lady Ren is always busy.
Her work truly never ends.
It's a young woman's game for sure.
You did good protecting the
civilians, preventing pandemonium.
The police department expressed
their gratitude as well.
All in a day's work for
the Demon Defense Force.
However, this mission
proved a valuable point.
Commanders can have trouble
protecting the innocent.
I wish there was a way to keep
all the fights here in Mato.
Little Miss Yakumo could
join in with her full powers.
Supreme Commander, now is the
time to go on the offensive.
The level of risk to
the world has increased,
so the Demon Defense Force
will need to shift strategies.
That said, there's still much we lack,
including our enemy's stronghold location.
We need to do reconnaissance.
Kuusetsu might be willing to
talk since she's inside me.
Although, she's only
appeared to me one time.
For now, I declare a state
of emergency for Mato. What?
What exactly does that entail?
I reveal the Eight Thunder
Gods' existence to the public,
and the Demon Defense Force pours
all its efforts into defending them.
We'll coordinate closely with
the leaders of the real world.
So we calm everyone's fears by
relaying our actions with humans?
Yes, of course, Lady Wren.
I understand.
A state of emergency.
The eight Thunder Gods are
not to be taken lightly.
I want you to brush up on your abilities
in preparation for the imminent attack.
Yes, ma 'am!
Why do you do that?
I like it in here because
you're big and comfy cozy!
The snag is a bug in a rug!
Jouryuu, I need you to come with me.
The Eight Thunder Gods have
been summoned for a meeting.
Shikoku, Jouryuu...
Come to greet us, Jakun.
Of course, it's my job as the youngest.
The rest are waiting inside.
Is your research coming along well? Yes.
There's still so much I want to learn.
Ordinarily, I'd be hard at
work at this very moment.
If not for those Demon
Defense Force pests!
You're very late.
I'm surprised you dodged that?
I figured you're moping, Lucky Rusty!
Actually, my anger is fueling my power.
That's what I call a Thunder God!
Between the two of you, I'd say
Shikoku seems a bit more upset.
I am responsible for this.
I never should have let
Kusetsu go into battle alone.
Then let's annihilate those vile
humans and avenge her death.
Lady Takeoku.
Take a knee, Shikoku.
I trusted in you to lead on my behalf.
since I cannot leave Mother's side.
The slaughter of a god is a
massive failure on your part.
I am horribly regretful with my decision.
Your wounds will heal
shortly, unlike hers.
So revel in your suffering.
Do not dwell on the thought
of Kusetsu any longer.
Thus, I have passed judgment upon you.
None of you are to chastise
her any further. Understood.
We never did that in the first place.
Taikyoku was the only one chastising her.
Now then,
normally when the eight of
us are gathered together,
we would have mounted an offensive.
What's the plan, Shikoku?
The demon defense force is
stronger than I anticipated,
which is why we should
rush the purification
day like we had planned
for after our attack.
If we wait for purification
day, then it's open season.
Our strength will increase dramatically.
Defeating the defense
force will be even easier.
Absurd!
Spineless approach!
How long does it take to
get our ducks in a row?
I suggest you tread carefully.
They annihilated one of our own!
We should retaliate!
I agree with Naruhime and Rai-ren.
All right, then how about a compromise?
We proceed with Shikoku's plan, and then
we make a move on the Demon Defense Force.
The Holy Tributes will attack them.
The Holy Tributes.
Former humans granted power by the gods.
The most capable of the holy
tributes becomes a thunder god.
They'll jump at any chance
to prove themselves.
She, too, desires godhood.
Fine by me.
Then we'll see if she's strong
enough to stand beside us.
What say you, Lady Taikyoku?
I do not mind so long as
Shikoku is in agreement.
Then it's settled.
Riren, Fukuma, the three of us
have things to discuss later.
You look like you're
planning something big.
Well, as the humans like
to say, go big or go home.
Hell yeah, as we should.
Mother wishes for at least
1,000 executions per day.
Carry out your duties with that in mind.
Make them fall to their knees
and bow down before our might.
A state of emergency for Mato.
This is starting to get pretty serious.
The eight Thunder Gods are on the move,
and they've already reached
havoc on the real world.
As for us, things are changing now.
We need to become stronger than ever.
What do you mean, stronger than ever?
First, by expanding our
respective abilities.
Then next, by enhancing my skills.
From now on, I'll be more
proactive about lending it out.
To you all, and other commanders.
The 7th Squadron is going to
get stronger alongside Yuki.
Don't let the Thunder Gods scare you.
We'll make them fall and bow down.
Great!
If that's the plan, Yuki, then
let's practice after this.
Himari, you've been keeping
Yuki all to yourself lately.
You have to share.
It's my turn now.
Nii's ready to work hard. Sure.
I'll train with you whenever you want.
Name the time and place.
You really mean it?
Then let's get going right now. Okay.
Hey, no fair!
Well, I'll take turns, okay?
Then I get to go next.
He wants to train you!
Whoa, hold on!
Everyone, hold on!
Good job back there.
You handled it very well.
Thank you, Miss Kyoka.
Practicing with Mato, reuniting
with Aoba, the commander's meeting.
Things have been hectic
since beating Kusetsu.
Yeah, they sure have.
I feel like I could drop
at any second. I know.
Take the rest of the day off.
That's an order as your commander.
Right.
Once you've had some decent rest,
do you think you'd want to
start training with me again?
Absolutely!
We have to get as strong as possible!
You have to surpass Commander Ren so
that you can become Supreme Commander,
Miss Kyoka!
Very well said.
Now that's my partner.
I don't know what
I'm
talking
about.
Love this love.
The love you don't.
It doesn't.
Life.
Online.
On the выполnce.
Melinda.
And.
Bye. Mod. Maybe.
Un gradual.
Why. Ms.
Love, love, follow!
A love that will change the world?
A dark time will shine with me!
Supreme Commander!
I had some free time so I stopped by
Kyoka?
She's with the first squadron.
She had some things to discuss with Ryu.
Oh, darn.
I picked a bad time.
Were you in the middle of cooking? I was.
Time to dig in.
The Supreme Commander
eating a meal in our dorm.
What a bizarre sight!
It's amazing.
Even the way she eats is pretty.
Thanks for the food.
Oh, it was nothing.
Oh, thank goodness!
She ate every last bite.
It was delicious.
A dish that evokes the season.
Now your reward.
Yuki sits.
When I say sit, it means.
Like this.
Who's a good boy?
You like that, don't you?
What in the hell?
Behind the ears, huh?
Is happening right now!
This isn't the same at all.
When Yuki Wakura's in his
human form, it's pointless.
I have to discipline him after
his slave transformation.
If not, it doesn't count as
payback for what he did to me.
I'll definitely be back.
Whoa, don't panic.
There's a bonus, I promise.
Too bad they didn't get
to see too much of us.
I'm so relieved I didn't have
to do any special training.
It's going to be a fierce battle.
I expect you all to do great things.